internationalcollegecounselors.com 2019-11-30

# Privacy Policy - International College Counselors

International College Counselors operates https://www.internationalcollegecounselors.com. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the site.

**Information Collection and Use**

Individuals who inquire about our services through the “Contact Us” or “Chat with Us” sections of our website provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name, e-mail address, and phone number.

Additionally, members of the general public who attend our seminars and workshops, or meet with ICC representatives at college fairs or other events, may choose to provide their e-mail addresses in order to be included in our mailing list. We use this contact information to disseminate helpful admissions information in the form of a weekly blog, as well as e-mail updates about our company and services.

For individuals who use our site’s “Chat” feature, location and IP Address are displayed on the chat dashboard while the chat agent is online. However, that information is not stored anywhere after the user leaves the site or quits the chat.

Finally, traffic and data tracking services including Google Analytics and Search Console collect anonymized data from visitors including search query, website referral source, time on site, pages per visit, geographic location, and demographic data if available.

**Data Storage and Sharing**

Personal information collected from our website and local sign in sheets is stored securely in Constant Contact and Salesforce.

Since the implementation of GDPR, Google stores traffic and tracking data obtained through Google Analytics and Search Console in our company’s accounts for no longer than 50 months.

International College Counselors maintains strict sensitivity and confidentiality concerning all user information and material. User information is never shared with third parties.

_By agreeing to work with International College Counselors or by submitting personal information to us, you are agreeing to the terms of this privacy policy and acknowledge that your information will be handled in accordance with this policy._

Last updated: May 2018
